{
    "subject": "resource/The_Starting_Line",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "The Starting Line",
    "human_readable": "The name of The Starting Line is The Starting Line.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9665998816490173,
            "question": "What is the name of The Starting Line?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9251407384872437,
            "question": "What kind of thing is called 'The Starting Line'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9177882075309753,
            "question": "Is there a specific context for the name 'The Starting Line'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9101926684379578,
            "question": "Is 'The Starting Line' a common name for something?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9037641882896423,
            "question": "Does The Starting Line have a different name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8233391046524048,
            "question": "Can you give an example of something that might be called 'The Starting Line'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8027500510215759,
            "question": "Are there any other names similar to 'The Starting Line'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.720393180847168,
            "question": "Why do you think 'The Starting Line' was chosen as a name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6210430264472961,
            "question": "Could you tell me more about The Starting Line?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6201766729354858,
            "question": "Is there anything else you know about 'The Starting Line'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of The Starting Line is The Starting Line.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5465_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could you tell me more about The Starting Line?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5465_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why do you think 'The Starting Line' was chosen as a name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5465_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other names similar to 'The Starting Line'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5465_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5465_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5465_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5465_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5465_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5465_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5465_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5465_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5465_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5465_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5465_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe query \"The name of The Starting Line is The Starting Line\" aligns with the context provided, particularly in documents like `93.txt`, which mentions a definition for \"starting line\" and does not suggest any different terminology. The information supports that the starting line is named as such."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}